Finding Aid for the John J. Bonica Papers Biomed.0118
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Lectures
  - Sleeved Slides
    - BX. Anatomy and Physiology of Respiration [Boxed Slides] [7 sleeves]. (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - CM. Chase Manhatten [3 sleeves]. (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - GE. General and Miscellaneous Slides [3 sleeves]. (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - HA. History of anesthesia [2 sleeves]. (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - JS1. Jail Study [#1] [2 sleeves]. (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - JS2. Jail Study [#2] [4 sleeves]. (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - MC. Multidisciplinary Clinic [3 sleeves]. (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - RA. Regional [1 sleeve]. (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - SP. Spanish Slides [5 sleeves]. (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - UN1. [untitled #1] [4 sleeves]. (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - UN2. [untitled #2] [3 sleeves]. (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - UN3. [untitled #3] [3 sleeves]. (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - 01. Sympathetic nervous system. (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - 02. Acute pain services. (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - 03. Italian pain slides. (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - 04. History of pain concepts. (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - 05. Development and current status of regional anesthesia. (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - 06. [Spanish slides]. (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - 07. History. (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - 08. Regional anesthesia for surgery. (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - 09. Venice discussions (Wrestling with Pain) [nice JJB personal slides]. (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - 10. Obstetric analgesia and anesthesia. (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - 11. Sympathetic block technique. (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - 12. Diagnostic and therapeutic nerve blocks. (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - 13. Neurolytic blocks. (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - 14. Celiac and lumbar sympathetic nerves ][cont'd in folder 3]. (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - 15. Epidural. (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - 16. Anatomy of pain. (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - 17. Obstetric epidural. (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - 18. Contributions and role of anesthesiologists in pain. (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - 19. [Pain responses]. (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - 20. Celiac plexus. (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - 21. Responses to N S. (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - 22. Cancer pain-Italian. (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - 23. Clinical pain service. (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - 24. Celiac plexus block. (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - 25. Anatomy of upper limb. (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - 26. Subarachnoid blocks. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 27. Anesthesia for critically ill. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 28. Therapy of cancer pain. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 29. Assessment of chronic cancer pain. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 30. Chronic pain (Upjohn). (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 31. Pain control in mass casualties. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 32. Local anesthetics pharmacology. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 33. Italian slides. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 34. Development of anesthesiology in USA. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 35. Neuralgia. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 36. Cervical plexus block. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 37. Neuralgia [cont'd in folder 5]. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 38. [?] and block of lower limb. (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - 39. WFSA talk-Manila. (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - 40. Effects of LEB alone vs. (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - 41. Peridural-anatomy, technique. (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - 42. Pharmacology of local anesthetics [cont'd in box 158, F1]. (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - 43. Causes and mechanisms of cancer pain. (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - 44. 3-1 block. (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - 45. Neurophysiology book illustrations. (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - 46. Chronic pain. (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - 47. Head and neck pain. (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - 48. Pain center. (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - 49. Epidural. (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - 50. Orofacial pain [cont'd in folder 2]. (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - 51. Block of lower limb. (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - 52. Historical development of anesthesiology. (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - 53. Cranial nerve block. (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - 54. Reasons for deficiencies (2nd). (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - 55. 25th Anniversary. (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - 56. Toxemia. (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - 57. Chronic pain-future goals. (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - 58. Caudal. (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - 59. Regional anesthesia for surgery. (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - 60. Cancer of head [cont'd in folder 3]. (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - 61. Myofascial pain syndromes. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 62. Family slides. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 63. Statistics on chronic pain. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 64. Pain modulation psych. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 65. Department of anesthesiology. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 66. Clinical pain service. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 67. Sympathetic supply to vessels of limbs. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 68. Cancer pain statistics. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 69. Historical development. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 70. Historical development of diagnostic and therapeutic nerve blocks. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 71. Therapy of chronic pain. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 72. Facial pain. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 73. Future trends and goals. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 74. OB A & A service (old). (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 75. Cancer pain 1989 Milan (Italian). (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 76. Italian slides. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 77. Cardiac pain. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 78. Development of anesthesia (2nd series). (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 79. Effects of increasing levels of SAB and LEB on circ and resp. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 80. Axillary upper arm. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 81. Spanish. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 82. Pharmacia Deltec. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 83. Peripheral vasc. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 84. Cancer pain-reasons for inadequate therapy. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 85. Cont SAB and epinephrine at T10->T1. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 86. Cancer pain statistics. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 87. Cancer pain patients. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 88. UW ARC. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 89. Complications of regional anesthesia-French. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 90. Parturition pain study. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 91. Block of cranial nerves. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 92. WFSA 1977 and older. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 93. Post-thoracotomy. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 94. Cardiac pain. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 95. Subarachnoid block. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 96. WHO. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 97. Pediatric pain statistics. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 98. Cancer pain-Italian. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 99. Intercostal [con't in 159 F1]. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 100. Epidural. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 101. Mechanisms of Chronic Pain. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 102. Myocardial InfarctionMyocardial Infarction. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 103. Cancer Pain. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 104. USSR. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 105. Obstetric A & A. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 106. Pharmacia Deltec Bonica Pain '87. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 107. Regional Anesthesia--early studies. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 108. IASP 2nd. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 109. Upper Ext Block. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 110. Murphy's Sayings re: Pain. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 111. Dr. T. Murphy [includes Filicudi poster photos]. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 112. Status of Therapy. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 113. Effect of SAB + LEB on Ventilation (Freund). (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 114. Cape Town. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 115. Role of Obst[etrician] in O[bstetric] A[nalgesia and] A[nesthesia]. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 116. ARNMD Cancer Pain Statistics. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 117. Bonica demonst[rations] in SE Asia. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 118. Acute Pain. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 119. Ithaca [1990]. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 120. [Temple University Health Sciences Center] [cont'd F2]. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 121. MD Pain Center Slides from Brian Ready. (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - 122. Obstetric A & A. (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - 123. Wrestling. (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - 124. [Slides from slide carousel re: upper extremity block]. (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - 125. [Slides from slide carousel re: regional anatomy]. (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - 126. [Head anatomy]. (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - 127. Thermograph. (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - 128. Slides for Columbus. (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - 129. Cancer Pain. (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - 130. [Port-a-Cath]. (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - 131. Chronic Pain. (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - 132. Ciba 11/20/85. (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - 133. McDonald Ohio State visit. (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - 134. [National Pain Foundation]. (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - 135. Neurophysiology of Pain. (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - [Miscellaneous slides, no order]. (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - [Miscellaneous slides, no order]. (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - [Miscellaneous slides, no order]. (Box 162, Folder unknown container)
  - Negatives
    - Cardiac arrest. Paper exhibit, 06 Apr 1948. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Vasoconstrictors in SAB, nd. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Teaching residents anesthes, 06 Oct 1954. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Copies, 19 May 1953. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Copies. Headache [?], nd. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Copies of charts of peridural, etc., nd. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Copies. Anatomy of circulation (heart), 13 Nov 1953. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Diagnostic and therapeutic. Paper, 28 Jan 1949. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Management of pain with nerve block. Exhibit, nd. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Peridural block, 30 Mar 1953. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Book. Copies or X-rays, 01 Nov 1951. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Endobronchial anesthesia. Exhibit, 19 Mar 1951. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Copies of figures. Book, 18 Oct 1957. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Pontocaine, nd. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Chart copies, 02 Sep 1949. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Role of anesthesiologist in intractable pain, 02 Oct 1951. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Copies, 12 Jan 1954. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Brachial plexus block. Paper, 27 May 1948. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Balance. paper, 28 Apr 1948. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Anesthesia in T.G.H., 05 Dec 1948. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Blood loss, nd. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - [Equipment and patient lying down], nd. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - European trip, nd. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Endobronchial. Paper, 30 Nov 1949. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Historical + control of pain, nd. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Pain clinic charts, nd. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Oxygen therapy. Paper, 19 Feb 1948. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Selection of anesthesia. Paper, nd. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Use of regional anesthesia for surgery. Exhibit, Aug 1951. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Book. Copies of [Hayworth and Wood roll ?], 11 Mar 1950. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Maps. Europe, 15 Oct 1954. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Copies. C-V disturb during anesth., nd. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Pain pathways, nd. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - C. pain. EEG, nd. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - [Unlabeled illustration negatives ], nd. (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - [Unlabeled loose negatives], nd. (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Cranial nerve blocks, nd. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - OB physiology (WFSA brochure & Marx chapter), 27 Dec 1971. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Pain. Typed slides, nd. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - de Jong--Physiology and pharmacology of local anesthetics, 27 Dec 1971. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - OB anesthesia statistics, 18 Feb 1972. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Hemodynamic responses to local., 04 Sep 1978. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - NCI site visit [2 envelopes], 10 Mar 1982. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Hipps, Linda, nd. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Pan-Pacific Surgical Meeting--Hawaii [2 envelopes], 14 Feb 1975. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Regional anesthesia studies re ARC, Aug 1978. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Cancer therapy and pain, nd. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - OB AA book, nd. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Miami Postgrad Meeting, 1978. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Arch Surg chapters, Nov 1978. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - OB slides, nd. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Regional anesthesia, 16 Oct 1978. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Anesthesia Research Center circular diagram, 30 Aug 1974. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - APS Science Writers Workshop, 09 Apr 1979. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Auckland, 1982. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - NIDR Program, nd. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - ARC slides, 24 Jan 1978. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - OB pain mechanisms and pathways--Innsbruck, 1979. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Slide negatives, nd. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Uterine blood flow, 18 Jun 1975. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - [No title], 18 Aug. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Epidural--epinephrine, 19 Jun 1975. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Australia--OB, regional, pain, IASP, Oct 1978. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Obstetric meeting--Hawaii. Typed charts, physiology diagrams, 14 Feb 1975. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - OB physiology (Dean Babbage lecture NY), 31 Jan 1975. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - OB--placental physiology, 11 Oct 1971. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - OB-regional anesthesia, 05 Feb 1974. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - Management of pain patients. Regional anesthesia f, nd. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)
    - 6840, 18 Aug. (Box 161, Folder unknown container)